adomnia.com 2011-12-31

# 

This Privacy Policy refers to the http://www.adomnia.com/ website and to each of its subdomains (e.g. http://subdomain.adomnia.com/). 

AdOmnia.com may update this Privacy Policy. AdOmnia.com shall not notify you about any changes; you must review this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to keep yourself apprised of any changes.   
You can find the most recent version of this Privacy Policy at: http://www.adomnia.com/privacy.php

AdOmnia.com collects information (e-mail and IP address) when you post ads, events and/or images. 

AdOmnia.com does not collect information when you respond to any ads. 

AdOmnia.com shall not rent, sell or give away any information to any third party, businesses or individuals. 

AdOmnia.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address. 

However, since each ad is publicly viewed, there is no convenient solution to ceasing malicious individuals and "spammers" from using the information in your ad(s) in a manner that you may not agree with. 

Companies which have placed advertising on AdOmnia.com may also collect information about you when you view or click on their graphical ads or text links.  
AdOmnia.com does not have any control over the collection of that information. You should contact those advertisers directly if you have any questions concerning your privacy and their advertising. 

**Children** : If you are under 18, be sure to obtain your parent or guardian’s permission before you send any personal information to AdOmnia.com.
